<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Krishan</title><link>https://krish-r.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Krishan</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:14:07 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krish-r.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tech</title><link>https://krish-r.github.io/tech/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 13:20:30 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://krish-r.github.io/tech/</guid><description> My current specialization is software testing and test automation.
However, I do some software development as well.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of some of the tech stack I&amp;rsquo;ve used/worked-with/explored/played-with over the years.
Legends (D): Development stack (T): Testing stack Languages (D &amp;amp; T) Java, Go, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, Lua Querying &amp;amp; Scripting (D &amp;amp; T) SQL, Shell Scripting Frameworks &amp;amp; Libraries Test Automation (T) Selenium, RestAssured, TestNG, Junit5, Playwright FrontEnd (D) Tailwind CSS, Hugo BackEnd (D) Go HTTP (Standard library) and Chi, ExpressJS, Flask (with Flask-RESTful) Command-line (D) Go Cobra Data Analysis and Wrangling (D, T) Pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib Databases &amp;amp; DataStore SQL (T) Oracle, PostgreSQL, SQL Server, Teradata, Netezza NoSQL (D) DynamoDB, MongoDB, CosmosDB In-Memory (D) Redis, H2 BI Reports (T) QlikView, QlikSense, SSRS, OBIEE, PowerBI Test Management Tools (T) Azure DevOps, JIRA, Confluence, HP ALM, HP QC Build Tools (T) Maven, Gradle Version Control and Remote Repository Hosting Services (D &amp;amp; T) Git with Azure DevOps, BitBucket and GitHub Cloud Services (T) Azure, AWS Containerization Tools (D) Docker CI / CD Tools (D &amp;amp; T) GitHub Actions, Azure DevOps, Jenkins, Apache Airflow Tracing, Monitoring &amp;amp; Visualization (T) Prometheus, Jaeger, Grafana Streaming Services (T) Apache Kafka</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://krish-r.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:14:07 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://krish-r.github.io/contact/</guid><description>GitHub
LinkedIn</description></item></channel></rss>